要是我能做决定
If it were up to me,
我不会让今年的圣诞到来
Christmas wouldn't even come this year.
你还能更像卡通里的坏人一点吗
Any chance you could sound more like a cartoon villain?
拜托  艾丽克斯  整整三天的冬日欢乐
Come on, Alex, it's three solid days of winter fun.
我们要坐雪橇  滑冰
We're gonna go sledding, skating,
冰钓  做雪天使
ice-fishing, make snow angels.
谁跟我一起  雪  雪
Who's with me?! Snow, snow!
雪  雪  雪  雪  雪  雪
Snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow, snow!
那是雪吗
Snow?
不是  那是叶子
No, that's a leaf.
这里比家里还热呢
It's hotter here than at home.
歌洛莉亚  你的每日邮件里
Gloria, in your little daily e-mails,
说的可是会很冷啊
you said it was gonna be cold.
我的手机上就是这么写的啊
That's what my phone said.
你用的是摄氏度
You're on celsius.
会很热哦  各位
It's going to be hot, guys!